ecommhub.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy - HubLogix

HubLogix Commerce Corp. (hereinafter “HubLogix”, “we”, “our” or “us”) Privacy Policy (“Policy”) sets out what information we collect, how we collect it, and what we do with it. If you have any questions concerning this Policy, please contact us as indicated in the How to Contact Us section below. We may update this Policy from time to time, so please check this Policy periodically for changes. HubLogix is the provider of a web-based drop shipping software and services that automate inventory management and order fulfillment for online stores that rely on third-party vendors, distributors, suppliers, or fulfillment centers for their inventory. Using the HubLogix platform, both retailers and suppliers can automate inventory management and order fulfillment, thus expanding product offerings, routing orders intelligently and minimizing backorders.

#### Your Information

As a provider of web-based software tools and services, we may collect two basic types of information, personal information and anonymous information – and we may use personal and anonymous information to create a third type of information – aggregate information. Personal and anonymous information may be collected directly from our customers and prospective customers, including when our customers or prospective customers communicate with us through our website located at https://hublogix.com (“Website”). We define “personal information” as information that is unique to an individual and might include the following: name, age, mailing address, zip code, other contact information, billing information, email addresses, and telephone numbers. We may collect certain information actively from users within our Website and other information passively (e.g., IP address). We will update your information whenever we can to keep it current, accurate and complete.

#### Our Use of Your Information

If we do receive your personal information, we will only use it for the purposes described where it is collected or otherwise described in this Policy, and we will not sell, license, transmit or disclose this information outside of HubLogix unless (1) you expressly authorize us to do so; (2) it is necessary to allow our service providers or agents to provide services for us, (3) it is necessary in order to provide our products or services to you (and to contact you when necessary), (4) subject to applicable contractual or legal restrictions, it is disclosed to entities that perform marketing services on our behalf or to other entities with whom we have joint marketing agreements, (5) subject to applicable contractual or legal restrictions, it is necessary in connection with a sale of all or substantially all of the assets of HubLogix or the merger of HubLogix into another entity or any consolidation, share exchange, combination, reorganization, or like transaction in which HubLogix is not the survivor, (6) it is necessary in connection with other business purposes including, without limitation, customer care, service quality, business management and operation, risk assessment, security, fraud and crime prevention/detection, monitoring, research and analysis, marketing, customer purchasing preferences and trends, dispute resolution, credit checking and debt collection, or (7) otherwise as we are required or permitted by law.

If you are a California resident, you may ask us to refrain from sharing your personal information (whether collected online or offline) with third parties for their marketing purposes. Please tell us your preference by contacting us as indicated in the “How to Contact Us” section of this Policy below. If you do not agree to Our Use of Your Information above, we cannot do business with you or authorize you to access our Website or use the HubLogix services available through our Website. Your continued use of our Website and the HubLogix services available through our Website and your continued payment of fees for access to HubLogix’s Website and services constitutes your acceptance of this Policy.

#### Direct Marketing Material

Subject to applicable contractual or legal restrictions, we may from time to time contact you with information on offers of goods and services, brochures, new products and forthcoming events. Our Website will assume you agree to electronic communications when you establish an account with HubLogix or request services online. You may indicate your preference regarding receiving third-party direct marketing material. If you do not wish to receive such information or would like to change your preference, please refer to “Your Rights” below.

#### Email

We appreciate your questions and comments about HubLogix and its products and services. Please see the “How to Contact Us” section of this Policy for instructions on how to send your questions and comments to us. We will share your messages with those within our organization who are most capable of addressing the issues contained in your message. We will keep a copy of your message until we have had an opportunity to address your concerns. We may archive your message for a certain period of time or discard it once it is no longer needed.

#### Your Rights

You have the right to ask in writing not to receive direct marketing material from us. If available, you can amend your previous preference by indicating as such in the “How to Contact Us” section of this Policy or refer to our literature (including the email sent to you by us) containing unsubscribe instructions. Once properly notified by you, we will take steps to stop using your information in this way. Please allow us a reasonable period of time in order to satisfy your request.

#### Use of Tools, “Cookies” and Links to Other Websites

If our contact and dealing with you is via our Website, we may use ÒcookiesÓ. Cookies allow us to identify your computer, but not you personally. You can set your web browser to refuse cookies. However, you may not be able to enjoy access and use all of the services available to you on our Website.

However, if you also receive our email marketing, we will tailor the information we send you unless you tell us not to. This means we may use information we hold and cookies to identify your individual website search behavior and preferences. This will enable us to send you more personalized and relevant communications. You will be given the opportunity on every communication to opt-out of this personalization.

We may collect information relating to customer trends and patterns and use cookies and software tools to measure site usage and related information. If you or your customers are making a purchase, we may also use cookies to keep track of the transaction from one web page to another.

In addition to the information we collect from cookies, we may also obtain information which you provide to us online – for example, when you establish an account with HubLogix or accept HubLogix services, including installing any HubLogix applications or when you purchase any HubLogix products or services, or otherwise when you communicate with us. In some cases, we retain both the cookie information and/or the information you provide to us online – for example, to complete a transaction you requested or to keep historical records of your past transactions. In other cases, we only retain the cookie and/or online information you give us if you request us to do so for your use in subsequent sessions.

An Internet Protocol (“IP”) address is a unique identifier that certain electronic devices use to identify and communicate with each other on the Internet. When you visit our Website, we may view the IP address (which may indicate the city, domain address and service provider) of the device you use to connect to the Internet. We use this information to determine the general physical location of the device and understand from what regions of the world our Website visitors are originating. We also may use this information to enhance our Website and services.

Certain pages on our Website contain “web beacons” (also known as Internet tags, pixel tags and clear GIFs). These web beacons allow third parties to obtain information such as the IP address of the computer that downloaded the page on which the beacon appears, the URL of the page on which the beacon appears, the time the page containing the beacon was viewed, the type of browser used to view the page, and the information in cookies set by the third party.

HubLogix uses Google Analytics, which is a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics uses cookies to help analyze how individuals use the services. The non-personal information generated by the cookie about your use of the Website and any applications available through the Website will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google will use this information for the purposes of evaluating your use of the Website and its applications, compiling reports on Website and application activity for our purpose, evaluation and providing other services relating to activity on and usage of the Website and its applications. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. You may disable cookies within your browser as described above; however, please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of the Website or applications. By using this Website or any of its applications, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above. For certain browsers, you can also prevent Google from collecting information (including your IP address) via cookies and processing this information by downloading this browser plugin and installing it: http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.

#### Children

We are committed to preserving online privacy for all of the visitors to our Website, including children. Our Website is a general audience website, and we do not knowingly collect information about children or provide services to children. Consistent with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act, we will not knowingly collect any information from children under the age of 13. The HubLogix Website is not designed to attract anyone under the age of majority in the applicable jurisdiction.

#### Monitoring

To ensure that we carry out your instructions accurately, improve our products and services and for security, we may monitor and/or record: (1) telephone calls; (2) activities using CCTV in and around our premises; and (3) transactions and activities on our Website. Recordings are and shall remain our sole property.

#### Security Statement

We have taken reasonable steps and have in place appropriate security measures to protect your personal information, including keeping your financial information private and safe. You acknowledge, however, that no transmission of data over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure, despite our efforts. Thus, while we will use commercially reasonable means to ensure the security of information you transmit to us, we cannot guarantee that such information will not be intercepted by third parties.

#### Visiting Our Website from Outside of the United States

If you are visiting our Website or purchasing our services from outside of the United States or otherwise contacting us from outside of the United States, please be aware that your personal information may be transferred to, stored or processed in the United States, where our servers are located and our central database is operated. The data protection and other laws of the United States and other countries might not be as comprehensive as those in your country, but please be assured that we take steps to protect your privacy. By using our services or purchasing our products, you understand that your information may be transferred to our facilities and those third parties with whom we share it as described in this Policy.

#### Links to Other Websites

For your convenience, we may provide links to other websites and web pages that we do not control. We cannot be responsible for the privacy practices of any websites or pages not under our control, and we do not endorse any of these websites or pages, the services or products described or offered on such sites or pages, or any of the content contained on those sites or pages.

Certain personal information may be made available to third parties using software tools, including application programming interfaces (API). Use of third party applications developed using those APIs are subject to the terms of use and privacy policies of such third party developers. You should be aware that such APIs may expose user information and you should review their terms appropriately.

#### Changes to this Policy

We may change this Policy at any time and from time to time. Any changes to this Policy will be either posted on our Website, included in a brochure and/or made available on request. The most recent version of the Policy is reflected by the version date located at the bottom of this Policy. This Policy is not intended to and does not create any contractual or other legal right in or on behalf of any party.

#### How to Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Policy or would like to learn more about how we protect privacy, please write to us at [support@hublogix.com](mailto:support@hublogix.com "Email HubLogix Support") or call us at 858-652-6444.

This Privacy Policy was last updated and posted on July 2016.
